# MOINAK DAS

WEB DEVELOPER

34 44 77ST - New York, NY





Moinak.Das@stonybrook.edu

## CARFFR PROFILE

Software developer with 3 years of experience in website management and software development for non-profit organizations. Fluent in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, python, php, java, and C#. Have experience with Android Studio, Unity Game Engine, and WordPress.

#### EXPERIENCE

## SOFTWARE DEVELOPER/ FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER - MAY. 2019 - JAN. 2021

**GREATER ASTORIA HISTORICAL SOCIETY** – Long Island City, NY

Developed WordPress plugins to streamline website submission processes | Designed new organization website: astorialic.org, tripling user traffic | Created software to automate day-to-day tasks and complete them in a fraction of their original time | Involved in the development and design of PC and mobile applications | Used Android Studio and Unity to develop prototypes for these applications | Effectively communicate ideas through PowerPoints and documents

SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER - SEP. 2020 - JAN. 2021

MARNI HALASA'S CITY COUNCIL CAMPAIGN - Manhattan, NY

Designed a new WordPress website to promote the campaign | Supervised two Junior Web Developers to develop the website | Worked with the campaign team to effectively represent Ms. Halasa online

INSTRUCTOR - SEP. 2020 - FEB. 2021

STUYVESANT STUDY SOCIETY - Manhattan, NY

One on one tutoring with a fourth-grade student | Created engaging lesson plans and online demonstrations

INSTRUCTOR - JUN. 2020 - SEP. 2020

**NEW YORK YOUTH TECHNOLOGY** – Queens, NY

One on one tutoring with a fourth-grade student | Created engaging lesson plans and online demonstrations

IT MEMBER - JAN. 2019 - JUN. 2021

STUYVESANT STUDENT UNION - Manhattan, NY

Managed IT help desk for the Student Union website | Managed website: Stuyactivities.org

INSTRUCTOR - JUN. 2019 - SEP. 2019

SCIENCE ADVENTURE KIDS - Manhattan, NY

Managed social media platforms | Responsible for animal care, cleanings, and feedings | Taught children aged 5-10 various topics in science | Helped children with disabilities keep up with instruction | Communicated effectively with both children and coworkers

CONTENT MANAGER - JAN. 2019 - JUN. 2021

STUYVESANT SPECTATOR WEB DEPARTMENT - Manhattan, NY

Responsible for the submissions of articles to the School newspaper website

# EDUCATION

STONY BROOK UNIVERSITY (2017-2018) - Brooklyn, NY

**GPA:** 3.76

STUYVESANT HIGH SCHOOL (2018-2021) — Manhattan, NY

**GPA:** 4.0

BROOKLYN TECHNICAL HIGH SCHOOL (2017-2018) - Brooklyn, NY

**GPA:** 4.0

#### SKILLS

Able to speak in Spanish and Bengali | Autodesk Certified Professional 2017-2021 | Experienced with Autodesk Inventor Professional, Fusion 360, and Blender